greyscalegorilla.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Greyscalegorilla

**Last updated:** May, 25, 2018

Greyscalegorilla Inc. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the [https://greyscalegorilla.com](https://greyscalegorilla.com/) website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at [http://www.greyscalegorilla.com/terms-of-service/](https://greyscalegorilla.com/terms-of-service/)

**Information Collection And Use**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name, and physical address (“Personal Information”).

We collect this information for the purpose of providing the Service, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests/inquiries, servicing your purchase orders, and improving our services.

**Log Data**

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data includes information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service’s functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Help feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie.

If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Service and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

**Do Not Track Disclosure**

We support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

**Service Providers**

We employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.

Those who purchase or license X-Particles through Greyscalegorilla Inc. grant access of Personal Information to Insydium LTD. for licensing and maintenance purposes.  Their Privacy Policy is available here: <https://insydium.ltd/insydium-ltd-privacy-policy/>

By completing a purchase on our website, your email address and purchase contents are stored with MailChimp (The Rocket Science Group) for sales analysis and marketing purposes. You must opt-in to marketing emails by checkmarking your interest on the checkout page. Their Privacy Policy is available here: [https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)

By expressing interest in our products and entering in your email address on the checkout page, your name, email address, and cart contents are shared with our marketing tool Jilt, owned by SkyVerge, Inc. for marketing purposes. Their Privacy Policy is available here: [https://jilt.com/legal/privacy/](https://jilt.com/legal/privacy/)

By completing a purchase on our website and choosing to join our Slack community via the opt-in checkbox, you agree to share your email address with Slack Technologies, Inc. for invitation and account creation purposes only. Their Privacy Policy is available here: <https://slack.com/privacy-policy>

By contacting our support via our support form or emailing support, you agree to share your name and email address with our support platform provider Salesforce, Inc. for support purposes only. Their Privacy Policy is available here: <https://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/>[ ](https://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/)

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

  * Stripe
  * PayPal

Their Privacy Policies can be viewed at [https://stripe.com/us/privacy](https://stripe.com/us/privacy) and  <https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>

We have Data Processing Agreements with our hosting and backup providers.

**Your Data Protection Rights**

If you wish to update your personal information, you can do so at any time by accessing the Customer Area.

If you wish to request deletion or a portable version of your data, please complete this form: [Personal Data Request or Removal](https://greyscalegorilla.com/personal-data-export-or-removal-request/). Your personal information will stored within our backup systems for up to 30 days after your deletion request, but will not be restored back to the live website except in rare instances, i.e. recovery after a natural disaster.

You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” link in the marketing emails we send you.

**Communications**

If you choose to opt-in to marketing messages, we  use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

**Compliance With Laws**

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.

**Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.

**International Transfer**

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

**Links To Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

**Children’s Privacy**

Only persons age 18 or older have permission to access our Service. Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 25, 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email. [support@greyscalegorilla.com](mailto:support@greyscalegorilla.com)
